<?xml version="1.0"?>
<story-manager-rpg>
    <campaign title="Northern Lights">
        <description>In Northern Lights the characters will explore everything that is happening in the northern countries, Aglium and Edra.
            In Stare, formerly Oclos, an aristocratic villain has just been twarted while in Ægis, an order of quasi scientific monks are trying to summon Doohlach, a demon that will wreak havoc over the world.</description>
        <books>
            <book-entry id="1" number-of-volumes="5" language="Seomakian">
                <titles>
                    <title>The Books of Sytar</title>
                </titles>
                <authors>
                    <author>Anluan</author>
                </authors>
                <published>
                    <year>378</year>
                </published>
                <subjects>
                    <subject>Religion</subject>
                </subjects>
            </book-entry>
            <book-entry id="2" number-of-volumes="2" language="Seomakian">
                <titles>
                    <title>The Codex of the Sisterhood</title>
                </titles>
                <authors>
                    <author>Condesendia Fortunatus</author>
                    <author>Consentia Fortunatus</author>
                </authors>
                <published>
                    <location>Æsis</location>
                    <year>4</year>
                </published>
                <subjects>
                    <subject>Religion</subject>
                    <subject>Occult</subject>
                </subjects>
            </book-entry>
            <book-entry id="3" language="Seomakian">
                <titles>
                    <title>Astronomy</title>
                    <title>A New View of the Stars</title>
                </titles>
                <published>
                    <location>Oclus</location>
                    <year>929</year>
                    <publisher>SU Press</publisher>
                </published>
                <subjects>
                    <subject>Astronomy</subject>
                    <subject>Astrology</subject>
                </subjects>
            </book-entry>
            <book-entry id="4" number-of-volumes="4" language="Seomakian">
                <titles>
                    <title>The Visions of Ylene</title>
                </titles>
                <subjects>
                    <subject>Religion</subject>
                </subjects>
            </book-entry>
            <book-entry id="5">
                <titles>
                    <title>The Origin of the Calendar</title>
                </titles>
                <subjects>
                    <subject>History</subject>
                </subjects>
            </book-entry>
            <book-entry id="6" language="Seomakian">
                <titles>
                    <title>The Ostean Calendar</title>
                </titles>
                <subjects>
                    <subject>History (ostean)</subject>
                </subjects>
                <description>This quarto is leather bound with metal clasps.
                    It's content is divided into three books, all in the same volume.
                    The first book describes the way the Occian astronomers viewed the stars, and how it differed from the Seomakian view.
                    The seccond book relates the observations made by the Occian astronomers concerning the movements of the heavenly bodies, with focus on the Sun and the Moon.
                    The third book is a detailed mathematical essay on how to calculate special dates.</description>
                <notes>Reading and fully understanding this book gives the reader an advanced mathematical skill of 2.
                    It also enhances the readers ability to perform rituals pertaining to the stars, sun and moon, making the task one step easier.</notes>
            </book-entry>
        </books>
        <locations>
            <location id="1" name="City of Æsis" country="Aglium" currency="GSC" language="Common" latitude="11.32" longitude="56.14">
                <description>Æsis is more or less in ruins today. The city is partly submerged and a few islands remain. Around the lake thus formed is currently buildings in extreme disrepair, mostly overgrown.
                    The City has some few inhabitants, and is also a place where the forrest gnomes living just outside finds &quot;thingies&quot;.</description>
                <notes>Currently a ritual is in progress in the city, aming at summoning Adramalech (as &quot;Doohlach&quot;).</notes>
            </location>
            <location id="2" name="Gnome Village" country="Aglium" currency="GSC" language="Common" longitude="55.8"/>
        </locations>
    </campaign>
</story-manager-rpg>
